[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAR MOTOR]
[CAR DOOR SLAM]
[AMBIENT MUSIC PLAYING]
[INAUDIBLE]
- Hey, you think they know ahead of
time what they're supposed
to say, or do the news people
just make it up?
[DING]
- It's not a fucking cartoon, Gary.
[TV INAUDIBLE]
- Hey, just turn that up.
- This isn't your living room, you know.
- Oh, if it was, you'd have
a beer in your hand,
and you'd be about ready to
give me a foot rub.
- Oh, yeah.
What about Gary?
- Gary, don't like foot rubs.
- Hey, I'd like a foot rub.
- Shut the fuck up, Gary.
[TV] That's right.
[TV] It's a gruesome scene here
in the Heights.
[TV] As far as we know, two were dead,
[TV] and one is critically injured.
[TV] The injured individual is being rushed
to St. Mary's Hospital
[TV] and is currently fighting for their life.
[TV] Eyewitness accounts report an
older model pickup truck
[TV] leaving the scene.
[TV] It is still preliminary, but
with the midnight
[TV] mangler on the loose--
[TV OFF]
- Hey!
- Not tonight, huh?
Oh, sorry.
You can just sit anywhere.
- Jesus Christ, "Mangler".
Who gives them these names?
- I'll tell you something what.
I give my left nut to run into one
of these serial killer types.
- Yeah?
- God damn right.
String them upside down like a buck
and skull fuck the bastard.
See how he likes that.
- That's just down the street from here.
- Yeah.
- Thank God we got out of there.
I do not need any more overtime.
- Cheers to that
- Right?
[DING]
- Order up.
- Then you wouldn't have any balls left.
- Huh?
- Because last week you said that
you'd give your right nut
if the Colts won.
- You're a dipshit.
Dipshit.
Sorry.
- All right, your mains are coming.
- Yo!
Let's go.
Yeah, I'm going to eat some food
in my belly's STAT.
If anyone--
- You can just grab a seat anywhere.
Oh, OK.
- Right here, you want to start right here?
- Fuck, be right here.
- Yeah, we're starving too, so--
hurry that shit up!
- Well, I'm not even supposed
to be here right now.
So--
Hi, can I help you?
- I don't know, can you?
- Would you like to see a menu?
- Uh, it's good to see you.
Sorry, it's been a long night. Some things didn't
go as I had hoped--
So, here we are--
What do you got that's good?
- It's been said that we have the
best steak in the country.
Oh shit.
Wow
The whole country?
- The whole country.
- Shit. All right. Maybe you'll
join me then.
- Join you?
- If I get the steak, will you join me?
Do you make it?
- I'm sorry?
- The steak, do you make it?
- No, there's--
Oh, that's too bad.
If you weren't
working, would you?
- Make you a steak?
- No.
Eat with me.
- Why not?
- Uh, because I don't know you.
- Yeah, but we would-- that's how we
would get to know each other.
Sit down--
Right, that's what regular
people do, right?
- You don't strike me as a regular person.
So.
- I walked into that one.
- Mm-hmm.
- Right.
No, you got a point.
- I'll grab a menu.
- Great.
Oh, hey, hey.
Coffee.
You have pretty eyes.
- I don't know why you're rolling out
- I'm hungry
-Shut up.
-It's gonna fucking get you--
-I really want some fries--
-That's some weak ass shit--
I don't know why you see him anymore.
-Hi, can I get you guys anything?
You got booze?
Uh, no, no booze. Just beer.
I'll get you guys a menu.
No, no, don't worry about it, Mom.
Dude, why are you so fucking ass?
- Mom?
- She means you old.
-As Fuck.
Oh, God, do you see her groceries?
Oh, fuck.
That's so cute. Don't think you
can smoke that in here.
All right, I'll get you guys a beer.
-Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I know her.
-You know her?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh, my God. You used to
babysit my little sister, right?
Dude, her name was, uh, Anna.
Anna, right?
- It's Anna.
- Anna, Nana. Holy shit, dude, I know.
- All right, do you guys want
to eat or what?
-Um, I mean, but what the fuck
happened to you?
- What does that mean?
- I mean, you're here, all this
shit, begging for tips,
like, weren't you supposed to be
a doctor or something?
- A nurse.
- Oh, my bad.
Okay, so let me guess. Someone
knocked you up.
- Oh, shit.
- Nice. Okay, nice. Yeah, so we'll
get some menus then, yeah?
And we'll take our time.
And why don't you run along there...
Mom?
- Okay.
[LAUGHTER]
-What a bunch of assholes.
-Yeah, well.
- Look, I'm sorry. We got off
on that wrong foot.
Feeling a little ornery tonight.
So...
- No worries.
- I'm sure you're used to it.
- Wouldn't you know it?
- Right?
I'm Charlie.
I won't be needing that. I'll
have the steak.
[whispering]
Oh, sorry I'm late, hon.
Jakey's daddy called me out of the blue.
He said he needed a lift, and I told
him that I had to go to work,
but he said it was an emergency
and you know me.
I'm a pleaser.
So I pick him up, drive him all
the way across town.
Through traffic, I get there and
I still might make it back,
and guess what?
- What?
- He forgot his phantom stick.
- What's a phantom stick?
- It's a game controller thing.
He calls it his phantom stick.
He won't play without it.
- A game controller?
- So I drive him all the way back.
- You drove all the way back for
a game controller?
- You know me. I'm a pleaser.
- Okay, well, I gotta go.
But just pick everything up. That's fine.
- Sure, I'll save your tips.
- No, no, no. Split them.
- You're an angel, you know that?
[kissing]
How is it out there?
- Same, you know. A bunch of drunk kids...
Oh, watch out for nine.
The guy's a creep.
- There's no one there.
- Oh, motherfucker.
- Thought you stiffed us.
- I needed my fix.
- Care for a drag?
- Oh, no, thank you. I don't smoke.
- It's all right. Neither do I.
Except on certain occasions.
How about that date?
- Look, um...
My husband is--
- You're not married.
You got no ring on your finger.
- My boyfriend is waiting for me.
- Wow.
- You have a good night.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
- I will scream.
- Why?
Let's just have a chat.
Platonically, outside work.
[MUSIC INTENSIFYS]
- Stop following me.
- Truck.
Right there.
- Go ahead.
- Actually...
Why don't you come with me?
No dice. You'll be on the ground before
anybody comes through that door
and i will be gone.
I just want to have a talk. That's all.
Please, I have a little girl.
Now, that is the first time you have
told me the truth all night.
[CAR DOOR SLAMS]
[JAZZ MUSIC FROM RADIO]
- I'm sorry if I always like--
- Could you ever see yourself
with a guy like me?
- Sure. Absolutely.
- No.
No, you're just saying that.
I'll save you the trouble.
You'd need vice grips to get that open.
- Look, I've just--
I've had just like a shit day, but I would
love to do something tomorrow.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. We could--
There's this place on Third Street.
It's so much better than here.
And we could like have a proper dinner.
- Sounds nice.
But you work tomorrow.
- I do. You're right.
But I would-- I could take the day off
no problem. I am due a night out.
- What would we do?
- Oh, man. Okay. So you--
You'd pick me up at eight.
- What would you wear?
- I have this--
I have this sexy outfit that I wear
only for special occasions.
It's like a little mini skirt,
a halter top.
- What about your underwear?
- It's great. You have to wait and see.
- I want the ones with Teddy
Bear's on them.
You know?
- Mm-hmm. Okay.
Okay. Let's wait till tomorrow, right?
We're going to do tomorrow.
- Just tell me you want me.
- No.
- Tell me you want me inside you.
- Please. Tomorrow
- No
Just tell me that you want to feel me
inside you and I'll let you go.
And then we'll talk tomorrow.
- Okay. Yeah. Okay.
I--
-want
- I-- I-- I want--
- To feel you...
- I want to feel you inside me.
- There you go.
[LOUD MUSIC]
- It's not a fucking cartoon, Gary.
[Warp Sound]
- Hey, could you turn that up?
- This isn't your living room, you know.
- Oh, well, if it were, you'd
have beer in your
hand, you'd be about ready to
give me a foot rub.
- Oh, yeah? What about Gary?
- Gary don't like foot rubs.
- Hey, I'd like a foot rub.
- Shut the fuck up, Gary.
[HAUNTING MUSIC]
[TV] That's right. This is gruesome
news here in the Heights.
[TV] As far as we know, two are dead and
one is critically injured.
[TV] The injured individuals think Rush to St. Mary's
[TV] Hospital is currently fighting
for their lives.
[TV] Eyewitness accounts report an
older model pickup truck leaving the scene.
[TV OFF]
- Hey!
- Not tonight, huh?
- Oh, you couldn't sit anywhere.
- Jesus, the "mangler" who comes up with these names?
- I'll tell you something, what?
- Then you wouldn't have any balls left.
-Huh?
- Because last week you said that you'd
give your right nut
if the colts won.
- You're a dipshit.
Dipshit.
You got a problem?
[HAUNTING MUSIC]
-Yo!
Oh, yeah, I'm going to need some
more of my belly STAT
- Just grab a seat anywhere.
- Yeah, we starving too, so...
hurry that shit up!
- Well, I'm not even supposed to
be here right now. So...
Hi, can I help you?
- Hi.
What is it today?
- It's the 15th.
- So Thursday, right?
- Couple more hours, yeah.
- And...
You don't know...
Me.
- I'm sorry, have we met?
- That's a good question.
- Is everything okay?
- I don't know.
- Sir?
- Sorry, is it...
Ever get deja vu?
- Every night, yeah.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Huh.
- Coffee?
- You have pretty eyes.
- Thanks.
Would you like to see a menu?
- I hear you have great steak.
- Best in the country, yup.
I'll have that.
Thank you.
[COOL MUSIC]
- How's your night?
Do you, uh...
Remember any of this?
Oh, the strong silent type.
Okay.
Doesn't talk that much.
I can get behind that.
But see, I recognize you.
Like you're familiar to me.
Have you been on TV?
If you're a cop, you have to tell me.
It's the law.
I get it.
Let's see.
Don't worry.
I've got a good memory.
- Thought you stiffed us.
- I needed my fix.
Care for a drag?
Sorry. That's right.
You don't smoke, right?
- Right.
- Well, I don't usually, but
beautiful night, huh?
- Sure.
- Kinda worth living twice.
What do you see when you look up there?
I don't see anything.
Supposed to be a...
vast universe full of wonder.
I just see dots.
- Great.
Have a good night. All right?
- Mm-hmm.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
- Can I help you?
- Sorry. Just...
going to my pickup.
- Oh, okay. Well, why don't you...
Go ahead.
- Right.
You know what?
Why don't you just come with me?
No.
No dice.
You will be spitting blood...
...before they get to that door.
Look at me.
I just want to talk.
That's it.
- I have a little girl.
- I know.
Let's go for a ride.
[LOUD JAZZ MUSIC]
[WARP SOUND]
- Hey, can you turn that up?
- No!
- Jesus.
- You're fucking with me.
Y'all... you're all fucking with me.
- Who the hell are you?
- You know me.
- And you're fucking with me.
Hmm? Aren't y'all?
- Sir?
-You--
You.
You, okay?
Okay.
This is a good joke.
Bravo.
Lift it up.
- Hey, man, that's not...
- I said shut the fuck up!
- Lift it up!
- Lift up your shirt!
- All right, now. I've had
about enough of it.
(gasp)
- I said...
Lift up your fucking shirt, or I'm gonna
put a bullet in your brain.
Nothing.
(sniff)
Nothing!
There's...
nothing.
Who are you?
Huh?
What the fuck is that?
Okay.
Uh, okay.
We are closed tonight!
[GUN SHOT]
Dip shit.
[WARP SOUND]
- Hey, you can turn that up.
- You fucking shot me.
- This isn't your living room, you know.
- Oh, if it were, you'd have beer in your
hand and you'd be about ready
to give me a...
- Hey!
- You fucking shot me!
- Sir, are...
Fuck you too!
- Hey, man...
- And fuck you!
- Fuck you.
- Hey, man, don't talk to the
lady like that.
[BELL DING]
Shut the fuck up Gary.
[CAR STARTS]
[WARP SOUND]
- Hey, can you just turn that up?
- Noooooo!
(panting)
[COMEDIC MUSIC]
No!
- Hey, can you just turn that up?
[GUN SHOT]
- You son of a bitch.
Turn that up, you fuck!
Turn it up.
No.
You don't get to disrespect me like that.
[WARP SOUND]
- Hey could you turn that up?
- This isn't your living room, you know.
-Oh, if it was, you'd have
a beer in your hand
and you'd be about ready to
give me a foot rub.
- Oh, yeah.
What about Gary?
- Gary don't like foot rubs.
-Hey, I'd like a foot rub.
- Shut the fuck up, Gary.
[TV] That's right.
[TV] It's a gruesome scene here
in the Heights.
[TV] As far as we know, two were dead,
[TV] and one is critically injured.
[TV] The injured individual is being rushed
to St. Mary's Hospital
[TV] and is currently fighting for their life.
[TV] Eyewitness accounts report an
older model pickup truck
[TV] leaving the scene.
[TV] It is still preliminary, but
with the midnight
[TV] mangler on the loose--
[TV OFF]
- Not tonight, huh?
- Jesus Christ.
"Mangler", who gives them these names?
-I'll tell you something what...
- That's just down the street from there.
- Thank God we got out of there.
I do not need any more overtime.
- Cheers to that.
[DING]
- Cause you, um, cause last
week you said that
- you'd give me a right nut
if the Colts won,
and then the Colts won.
- You're a dipshit.
- Just saying.
- Dipshit.
[HAUNTING JAZZ MUSIC]
- Can I help you?
- Hi.
- I'm good for right now.
Thank you.
- Sorry, you can't sit there
and not order food.
- Right.
- I'll have a cup.
- What do you think?
- About what?
- This.
This is real, right?
- As far as I know, yeah.
- How do you know?
-That this is real?
I mean, the coffee's hot, the night's
long, the customers are weird.
What more do you need?
- I think you're right.
- Well, that is very comforting.
-hmm
- What?
- On second thought, I'll have a steak.
It's a great choice.
- Yeah.
- You know, I still haven't placed you.
But I'll get it.
What would you do?
If you were me.
Let me ask you that.
See, because I'm caught in
like this time loop.
Like a hiccup in time?
It's a record scratch.
That just keeps like...
It just keeps repeating.
So...
What would you do?
Yeah?
Good talk.
-I...
No, I... I don't think I can...
- Come on, why not?
- Look, honey, I'm worried.
I don't know that I can.
I just...
- Hi.
- Can I help you?
- I don't know.
Can you?
- What is this?
Is this date night?
- Yeah, so?
You guys having a good time?
- Look, pal, I don't know who you are.
Can you just get out of...
- Let's not get all bothered.
All right? I just came to say hi and to get
to know you a little bit.
Why?
You guys married?
- Uh...
- Okay, look.
It doesn't matter to you.
-No, I'm asking her.
Shut the fuck up.
- Why is that a hard question?
- We're not married.
- Would you mind if I eat with you then?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, we mind.
- We're trying to have a nice night.
Me too.
[whispering]
- Okay, okay.
Fuck you.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
- Oh, shit.
- Shut the fuck up
Sit down.
All right?
Put your goddamn hands down.
Look, have a seat.
Shh.
- I don't want any trouble, man.
- Okay.
Listen.
You guys are married.
Just not to each other.
Right?
Your wife sent me.
-Shit.
- And I'm supposed to leave your body
out the dumpster in the back.
How do you feel about that?
- Okay, man.
Just, here, I got money.
Sure you do.
- Not even my type, but I think
this could be fun.
- Oh, shit.
Food's here.
Okay.
I was just fucking with you all.
Have a good night.
Really.
- So my wife didn't--
- Didn't hire me to kill you?
No.
No!
I'm just supposed to break your arm.
Fucking with you again.
No.
I'm going to kill you.
Not really.
I don't know.
Anyways, look.
Have a good night.
Enjoy.
On me.
And, you know, maybe you can do that
thing you talked about.
One more thing.
Forget I'm here.
Ah.
Gotta love it when you get back to your
table and your food is ready.
- You mean Edna and Gretchen?
- Yeah, Gretchen.
All day, every day.
- Gretchen at least jokes when
she craps herself.
Like she at least knows what she's doing.
Edna has to...
- Excuse me.
- Hi.
I saw you...
- At the bathroom.
- Yeah.
- You all from here?
- Sorry, you can't just sit there.
- Why not?
Nurses?
I can tell by the outfit
you're wearing.
Smocks
- You mean scrubs.
- Sorry I'm not from here.
- What, America?
- That's funny
-Yeah
- You need to try this steak.
- We were actually just leaving.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- You want me to walk you out?
There's a lot of bad guys out there.
- Hey, Anna.
We're all done.
Hey.
No more outside than in here.
Thanks buddy, we're good.
- Hey.
- I'm just going out for a smoke.
[Warp Sound]
- Hey, can you turn that up?
- I got it.
[TV] Another example of the scientific community
pushing boundries in this critical field
[TV] We're really doing great work.
[TV] We have a developing story in the
southeast heights where
[TV] our Alex Castillo is standing by with the latest.
[TV CONTINUES]
-That's a shame.
- Excuse me.
- Well, hello.
-You're not supposed to--
- You come here often?
I mean, I do.
Just a regular old-- regular?
- Sorry, do I know you?
- I don't know.
Does she?
Do you?
- Okay, yeah.
You're not supposed to be back
here, so if you could--
- Of course.
I'll have a beer.
And watch out for that guy.
Lock your doors.
- Fucking asshole.
- Goddamn right.
I'd string him upside down like
a buck and skull fuck the bastard.
See how he likes that.
- Yeah, then you wouldn't have any--
-Balls left.
You know what I'd do to him?
I'd tie him to the back of my truck
and I'd drag him around the block
until he was all tore up.
And then I'd dump gasoline on him
and I'd light his ass up.
But I'd have a fire extinguisher with me.
And I'd douse him with it.
I'd put him out just before he died
and I'd let him sit in it.
And then I'd do it all over again.
What are ya'll drinking?
I'll buy you beers.
Hmm?
It's good to be around like-minded
people like yourselves,
you know what I mean?
Midnight Mangler.
It's a hell of a moniker.
Right?
What do you think, man?
Good?
Catchy?
What do you think he looks like?
We'll have three more beers.
Hey.
We should do it.
We should definitely, definitely
do it to three of us.
- Do what?
- Catch the son of a bitch.
I'm not into the skull fucking.
I'm really not.
I'll let you figure that part out, but
we should definitely do it.
How do you keep the teeth from scraping
the...your...when you...doin it?
- The fuck are you talking about?
-The skull fucking!
The skull fucking.
That's right.
- Listen, mister, I can't listen
to this anymore.
This is a bit much for me.
- Yeah, you know what?
Hey, keep that cold.
I'll be right back.
[HAUNTING JAZZ MUSIC]
- Wait a minute.
I'm still here
Now what the fuck?
- Hey, hey, hey.
What are you doing in the
ladies' restroom?
- Oh.
- That's my cart too.
What the hell are you doing with my cart?
- Well...it was bad...
- you did get it cleaned all up then?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Step aside.
- Hey, look.
I better take it.
Trust me.
- If you're worried about the shit
around here, don't worry.
I'll do the shit all the time.
- How about this?
Let's just get it outside.
I'll help you.
That fucking Russian,
I tell him every fucking time
that the white boys,
they can't handle the
fucking carne asada.
What is this?
It's so fucking heavy, a la verga.
I told you.
What the fuck?
¿Que Chinga?
[GUN SHOT]
I told you it was messy.
- Sophie?
Hey.
Did you see my friend?
- No.
What, is she missing?
- Her car's still here, but...
- Damn, that's weird.
I got my pickup over there.
I could drive you around the
block and look for her.
She's probably around her, so...
- No, I'm good.
- You sure?
- Yeah
- Okay.
- Good luck.
- Red.
- You better not give me shit
about Sarah, okay?
Because you're the one how be
dating gargoyles.
- What are you talking about?
- Like this?
- Yeah. Lisa, are you kidding me?
[AMBIENT DIALOGUE]
- It's goddamn good to be alive, huh?
- You want another one?
I'll get you all another one.
Hey.
Three more, please.
- Did you hear that outside?
It sounded like gunfire.
- Nope.
Maybe it was the manger.
We should go.
We got work to do.
Let's do this.
Unless you're scared.
- Shut up, dipshit.
- Okey-dokey.
This is your last round.
After this, if you want more, go to
Lucky's. It's not a bar.
- Come on, Anna.
- I'm not dragging your pony ass
out of here again.
- I can't go back to Lucky's.
- Why not?
- What was that?
- Nothing.
- Hey, any luck?
- No, it's the strangest thing.
- What?
- Sophie's missing
- What do you mean missing?
- Well, she went to the bathroom and
then she just disappeared.
- Is her car still here?
-Yeah.
- Any of you knuckleheads see anything?
- He was outside.
- Having a smoke.
All right.
Well, good luck with all that.
- Why didn't she tell me?
Okay, you know what?
I'm going to be off soon.
I'll drive you, okay?
- It's fucking weird, right?
- Yeah
- I'm dying here, okay?
Babe, I got needs.
He's getting suspicious.
It just feels like you don't
want to spend--
- What are you doing, man?
- Fuck.
- What?
Oh, sorry.
No, don't mind me.
Keep going.
You were saying how she doesn't
prioritize your needs.
How does that make you feel?
Hey, look, it's been a long night.
I need a little entertainment,
you know what I mean?
Okay, come on, man.
If you don't mind your own business--
[gasping]
- If I don't mind my own business, what?
[gagging]
If a man commits adultery with
another, the man, the woman,
the adulterer and the adulteress
have to be put to death.
Leviticus 20.10, it's in the Bible.
Do you read the Bible?
Well, it's in there.
[THUD]
Oh, ah, sorry.
I just tipped my hit my thing on the--
hit the-- right?
You ever get that?
Whoo.
All right.
Well--
Oh, no.
You okay?
I think he's had a little
too much to drink.
Can we call a cab for him?
And you know what?
I'm gonna kill for some ice cream.
- Oh, my God, ma'am, ma'am, are you okay?
Are you--
No, no, no, no.
What are you doing?
- Everybody calm down.
God damn it, I guess there's no covering
that up, is there?
And don't.
-You're-- you're the--
- Yeah, yeah, you got me.
I'm the Mangler guy.
I was gonna kill you all quietly.
Don't worry, I'll figure something out.
- Fuck.
You know what? Why don't
you grab the booth?
- Why don't you go fuck yourself?
Get in the booth pretty please.
With cherries on top.
[screaming]
All right, well, there's one less
to deal with, yeah.
I'm warning you.
- Yeah, got it.
- What are we gonna do?
What are we gonna do?
I mean, I could just shoot y'all.
Like, shoot y'all.
1,2,3,4...
Well, where's the fun in that?
So what else are we gonna do?
Fuck!
Well, definitely no skull fucking.
You know what I mean?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, look, I'm--
Wait a minute.
Shit.
[CLANG]
[WARP SOUND]
I mean, I'm here for a reason, right?
I mean, so just hear me out.
If you are the Almighty or the, you
know, like a-- whatever.
Okay.
And you put a shark in a tank
full of guppies,
what do you think is gonna happen?
Shark's gonna eat, right?
That's--
I mean, how many times do you
think it's been--
Hey.
Watch this.
[ROCK MUSIC]
- Seriously?
Come on, dude.
[DIALOGUE INAUDIBLE]
[SCREAMING]
I'm a fucking god!
- Shit!
- Hey, you want to hold this for me?
- What?
- Do you want to hold this for me?
- Oh, no. Fuck no.
Yeah, I'll pass, man.
- Okay.
Wait, hey.
- Whoa.
Serious.
Dude, what the fuck is that?
- Ah too late
Dude, what the fuck, you sicko?
What the fuck are you doing?
Whoa, what the shit?
Dude, what the fuck, you sicko?
You good, man?
You--
Call somebody.
You okay?
- I'm on top of the fuck with the world.
- My friends, they know where I am, okay?
- You didn't flush.
- I don't fucking flush, no one fucking flushes
- You didn't flush!
- I normally don't!
- It's fucking disgusting.
You gotta be honest.
[SCREAMING] [GASPING]
[GASPING]
[FLUSH]
[MELANCHOLY CLASSICAL MUSIC]
- Hey can you turn that up?
- Are you okay?
[SCREAMING]
- You can grab a seat anywhere
- Hey can you turn that up?
- Just sit anywhere.
Just sit anywhere.
- Hey can you turn that up?
[DING]
- Order Up
- Hey can you turn that up?
- You can grab a seat anywhere
- I'd like a foot rub
Shut the fuck up, Gary.
[IN UNISON] Would you like to see a menu?
[IN UNISON] What are you doing?
- Okay, I'm gonna--
- Give me some coffee.
- Okay.
- I am so fucking tired of this.
- Back and forth between you and me.
- What are you talking about?
-Have you ever been intimate with someone?
Like you had the perfect moment.
And then the next day you're just
a fucking stranger.
Forget it.
Forget it!
Just-- I'm so fucking tired of this.
- What are you--
I'm gonna go get you a menu.
- No, I don't want a menu.
I want eggs and bacon.
-Sorry.
- Yeah, you cut out breakfast at noon.
I know.
But you had eggs back then.
All right.
You had them back there. They're
in the fridge.
Was that big fucking cook hiding them?
Hmm?
[DING]
Eggs.
Fucking--
Knew it.
- Sir.
- Jesus Christ.
- You're supposed to be here.
- Yeah, yeah. Just make me
some fucking eggs.
- Sir, you're very rude.
I suggest you find seat before
you find trouble.
- I'm getting real tired of your shit.
You hear me?
All your little sneaking around?
Huh? Like some little fucking bug?
I'm fucking God here!
- Well, Mr. High Mighty, I'll
help you find a seat.
But you get no fucking eggs.
You come my kitchen, tell
me how fry cook.
- That was a good one.
Okay, but let's do this.
Let's uh--
Let's set the ground rules.
- No rules of ground. You get
fucked from here, huh?
- You're gonna want to hear
what I have to say.
- So you show me gun.
- Yeah.
I mean, you know.
Because okay, because I'm saying no guns.
No guns.
Blades are allowed. Blades okay.
Nowhere critical.
And when I beat you, you make
me a fucking omelet.
And whatever's in there, because
that smells delicious.
Understand?
Da?
- Da.
- But no fucking eggs for you.
I've hit him in the nuts.
I played coy.
I tried to sneak up on him.
He's got this sixth sense, this KGB,
super secret agent thing going on.
All right, I just gotta-- I gotta
keep my head straight.
I gotta keep my head focused.
You know what I mean?
All right? I can't even sleep.
I don't even know what's going on.
Yes.
Yes!
Here it goes.
- What are you here for?
This is not for you.
- But I really just want some eggs.
And I thought maybe if I asked nice.
- You know, no served breakfast after 12.
- I know.
But I thought maybe you could
cut me some slack.
- No breakfast.
No slack would be cut.
- All right.
Let's get on with it.
Walk.
Push. Plate. Boom. Cup.
No. Fuck.
Punch, punch. Knee.
Punch, punch. Knee. Pit.
Balls.
Fuck.
Then...
Watch this.
Fuck. Yes.
Fuckin' giver.
Shut up!
Hey!
♪ (Air Supply - Here I Am) ♪
♪ Here I am. ♪
♪ Playing with those memories again. ♪
♪ And just when I thought time
had set me free. ♪
♪ Those thoughts of you keep taunting me. ♪
♪ Holding you. ♪
♪ A feeling I never outgrew. ♪
♪ Though each and every part
of me has tried. ♪
♪ Only you can feel that space inside. ♪
♪ So there's no sense pretending. ♪
♪ My heart it's not me. ♪
♪ Just when I thought I was over you. ♪
♪ And just when I thought I
could stand on - ♪
(gunshot)
(whispering and rumbling builds)
(dramatic music)
Hey.
No, hey!
- Sir?
- Hey, you see that guy?
- Who?
- He was...
Oh, I gotta get out of here.
I'm losing my mind.
- Yeah, maybe you should go home.
- I can't.
Don't you get it, I...
I don't even know where home is anymore.
- Would you like me to call someone?
- Who?
Who the fuck are you gonna call, huh?
I'll figure it out.
Go, get the fuck outta here.
You know what?
Look, coffee.
Thank you.
(dramatic music)
(tension in music building)
- Sir, you can't sleep here.
Sir, I'm sorry.
- No, no.
- Are you okay?
- I don't know, no.
(police radio chatter)
Hey, can I get some fucking coffee?
- (clears throat)
How we doing this evening?
- You know...
- Why don't you and I have a little talk outside.
- No, I can't.
- I really need you to come
outside with me.
- I don't think you understand.
- No, you don't understand.
You can do this your way.
Or you can do this the easy way.
- Fucking overtime, my ass.
- Wouldn't happen to be your truck
out back, would it?
- No!
I can't go outside!
Don't, don't!
Don't fucking do it.
- Hey, could you turn that up?
- Hi, can I help you?
- Dropped by fork.
- Excuse me.
- Hey, Marcus, could you help me
with the napkins in the stock room?
Can't find the stool.
- Hey, could you turn that up?
- Oh, you can grab a seat anywhere.
You're awesome.
- Hey, could you turn that up?
- Hi, can I help you?
- Dropped my fork.
- Excuse me.
- Hey, could you turn that up?
- Oh, you can grab a seat anywhere.
Hey, Marcus, could you help me
with the napkins in the stock room?
You're awesome.
- Oh, I dropped my fork.
- Excuse me.
- Are you okay?
Can I get you something?
- I don't know.
I don't know.
- What?
- Huh?
- You don't know what.
- Uh-uh.
You really disappoint me, you know that?
I thought he was a real one,
but just look at you.
You look like you're about to cry.
You gonna cry for me?
Charlie Sobhraj, Ted Bundy,
Domer, Ed Gein.
Them's real ones.
What would they do if they were here
in your shoes right now?
What would your daddy do?
- Don't you talk about my daddy.
- No?
Why's that?
- Because he's got nothing to do with
what's going on here.
So shut the fuck up about my dad.
- Alright.
What are you up to now anyways?
- 12.
- 12?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I've killed her like 20 times.
- Yet, there she is.
- So what the fuck am I supposed to do?
- I don't know.
That's for you to figure out.
But what I do know is, you
running around here
with your dick hanging out,
ain't getting nothing done.
Yeah - "I am fucking God."
What is that shit?
You like an idiot.
- I am -
- Am a worthless piece of shit.
What are you gonna do?
You gonna go back to your
booth and pout?
You gonna let them break you?
- I gotta get out of here.
- "I gotta get out of here." (mocking)
- I have killed all of them.
Everyone.
- Yet, there they are.
So I, uh - what are you saying? I gotta -
You think? If I -
I -
- Have you tried it?
- Expelled them all clean.
Not a peep.
Yeah.
(eerie music)
Don't forget to flush.
(eerie music) Hey, Marcos, can you
help me with the napkins
in the stockroom?
I can't find my sool.
Okay.
You're awesome.
Asshole.
Oops, I dropped my fork.
Oh, I'll get it for you, darling.
- Excuse me.
You know what, they're right there.
I'll be right back.
(eerie music)
(stabbing noise)
- Ma'am?
Excuse me, I think there is
a man over there.
He's having some serious issues.
(snapping)
(stabbing noise)
(eerie music)
- Fucking occupied, man.
What the shit?
(frantic stabbing noises)
(eerie music)
(slitting noise)
(stabbing noise)
- What the fuck?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
(stabbing noise)
(screaming)
Shh, shh.
(gunshots)
(gunshot)
- Hello, darling.
(eerie music)
Easy.
- Please, what do you want from me?
- Sorry, I'm late, hon.
Jakey's daddy called me out of the blue.
He said he did a lift and I told him,
I have to go to work, but he said
it was an emergency
and you know me, I'm a pleaser,
so I pick him up
and are you okay?
Why are you holding the gun?
(gunshot)
(screaming)
- Now it's just you and me.
Here we are, again.
This is the way it was meant to be.
Fuck the others.
Fuck them, no, hey.
You're special.
But I can't keep doing this.
I'm losing my fucking mind.
My fucking head, doing the same
thing over and over again
and again and again and I can't
sleep and I can't die.
But I figured it out.
I did it.
And you, you, you're my last.
Please, I have a daughter.
(stabbing noise)
- Hey, can you turn that up?
- This isn't your living room, you know.
- Oh, well if it were, you'd jave a beer in your hand
you'd be about ready to give
me a foot rub.
- Oh yeah, what about Gary?
- Gary don't like foot rubs.
- Hey, I'd like a foot rub.
- Shut the fuck up, Gary.
Hey.
(dramatic music)
(door creaks)
Just gonna fucking sit here.
(dramatic music)
(crying)
(screaming)
(dramatic music)
You real?
- Of course, my son.
Please.
(dramatic music)
- Why are you here?
- Why is anyone here?
- Not it.
Y- ou look tired.
- I can't sleep.
- What have you learned?
- Learned?
I, uh,
I wanna go home.
- But you're not ready.
- No.
I'm ready.
I'm very ready.
- Why are you here?
- I don't know.
- Yes, you do.
- No.
Salvation?
- Have you found it?
- No.
- Have you tried?
- I don't-
I don't think that, uh-
- What?
- I've done a lot of bad things.
(sighs)
- Though your sins are like scarlet,
they shall be cleansed white as snow.
Isaiah 1:18, but you know that
already, don't you?
The first step is to ask.
- I wanna see the trees.
And I wanna see them sway in the wind,
and I'm gonna hear the birds,
and watch the sunset.
I haven't cared about these
things before.
I don't know.
That, that was before, right? Except...
- Except when?
- Don't.
- You have to say it.
- No.
- Charlie.
- You have the whole world
at your fingertips.
You have the power to choose
your own destiny.
- This isn't real.
- What will you choose?
- If I were to take this knife and
drive it into your hand,
is it real?
Because it is, it's as real as it gets.
Now, tell me.
Tell me.
- I wanna be free.
(laughing)
I want forgiveness.
- There you go.
There you go.
How does it feel?
(sighing)
- Feels good.
- Hey.
(laughing)
- That's right.
- But what do I do?
I don't know what to do.
- Start over.
(somber music)
- Hey, can you turn that up?
- This isn't your living room, you know.
- Well, if it were, you'd have
beer in your hand,
you'd be about ready to give
me a foot rub.
- Oh yeah, what about Gary?
- I'll give you a foot rub, Gary.
- (from TV) We have a developing story in the Southeast Heights.
- Uh, can we not do that?
I mean, do we have to listen to that?
- I wanna see it.
- He's a bad guy doing bad things
and he hurts people.
Why don't we just enjoy our dinner?
- I'm with you.
(DING)
- Order up.
(cafe music)
- You think he'd really give me a foot rub?
- What are you doing?
- Just-
- Oh my God!
- I was gonna go back by my house.
- I thought she was gonna lie there.
- I'm gonna watch TV, babe.
- Yo!
How's it going?
- Who the fuck are you?
- What no, "hi", just, who
the fuck are you?
- Are you fucking serious?
Do we know you?
- Yeah, I don't know what you're trying
to sell us here, pal, but.
- Nope, not pals.
Why are you with these two clowns?
- Yo, fuck you!
- There you go again.
See?
Just listen.
This is where I normally blow
your fucking brains out.
However, I've had a change of heart.
- We don't want any trouble, so if--
- You do.
But not this trouble.
So, why don't you two get the
fuck out of here?
Diner's closed, so.
Don't fuck!
- Hey!
I know.
You okay?
Do you need a ride, cause I could
arrange one for you.
(sigh)
- I'm good, thanks though.
- Okay.
(doorbell ringing)
- Can I help you, doll?
- Pie.
I want pie.
- Okay, just any pie?
- All of it.
- We have a lot of pie.
- What's your favorite?
- Um, strawberry rhubarb.
- Oh, shoot. You're fancy.
- No, I'm not fancy.
- It's okay.
You deserve it.
Okay.
Um...
Yeah.
Could I get it heated up?
- Of course.
You want an ice cream on
the side, cowboy?
- Uh, yes, please.
- Okay.
- It's the pudding.
It's the pudding. It makes
it like watery.
- It's like a laxative. And I'm
like, they're old.
- Excuse me?
I know. Another annoying guy
hitting on you, right?
But I just saw you got off your
shift and nurses, right?
I just wanted to say thank
you for your service,
of all the jobs out there, and you two
pick one where you help people.
It takes a special kind of person
to do that, night after night.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, that's all.
Have a great night and the pie's on me.
- Oh, you don't have to do
that.
- Already done.
- Hey, what's your name?
- That
doesn't matter.
Have a great night. Me too.
- You too.
Free pie. I'll take it.
- What you do is you take the raw noodles
and you, like, throw them in.
You try and catch his...
- Would you mind if I...?
- Yeah, we do.
We're trying to have a nice-
- Have a nice night?
I know. Me too.
I get it. I...
Look, just gonna be a second.
But I don't even know where to start.
My mom. My mom, she...
My dad was a real son of a bitch.
He did a lot of bad things, and he put
hands to my mom on the regular.
And they tried to hide that from
us, but kids know.
And then, of course, he would cheat
on her all the time.
He didn't even try to hide that.
And my mom would take it out on us.
Vicous cycle.
Look, I don't know what you have going
on in your respective homes.
But.. Kids know. Everyone knows.
And think of them.
- Mr., I don't know what you think
is going on here...
- But don't be an asshole.
Take it or leave it.
- Another one?
- What? No.
No.
- I thought you were gonna have them all.
- I tried.
But, uh...
You know what? Three more.
- He said...
He said... "bananas..."
[laughter]
Because he was a monkey.
- How long does it take for
him to tell stories?
- A long time. Hanging out with him is kind
of like doing charity work.
- Hey there, cowboy.
You, uh... got one of those for me?
Sure.
[traffic sounds]
Here. Gotcha.
The stars are out tonight.
Look at them. It's like a fog
of stars up there.
- It's the Milky Way.
- Wow.
Wait.
We're in the Milky Way.
- Yeah, silly. We're part of it.
- Okay, but... if I can see it up there...
How's it...
Down here?
- You'd have to ask my daughter, Amy.
She's the astronaut.
- How old is she?
- Ten. But she loves her stars.
I mean, she could show you where
every constellation is.
- I think I'd like that.
Uh...
Can I walk you to your car?
- Sure.
- Well, um...
Be safe. There's...
Lots of bad guys out there.
- Is this your pickup?
- Uh, yeah. I like the...
old stuff.
- Well...
the night is still young.
- Come on.
Uh...
That one's broken.
Sorry.
- Of course.
[door slams]
What are you doing?
- I don't know.
Um...
I never...
- Come here.
- Why?
- What do you mean, "why," silly?
- Why tonight?
- Don't you feel this...
connection between us, or...?
Come here.
(somber music)
(gasps)
(stabbing noise)
- Well, that's it, isn't it?
I thought we were almost there.
- We were getting closer.
- How is she?
- She's fine.
You need a moment?
- No, no. I'm...
I'm okay.
- You sure?
- Mm-hmm. Just, like, a little bit
of a headache. I'm good.
- You can let the board go.
(earie music)
Good morning, sunshine.
Just relax.
Relax.
- Hey! Where am I?
- It'll take you a moment to get
your bearings back.
- How do you feel?
- You're not a priest.
- No, I'm Dr. Lovato.
Residence psychiatrist here at Nuroscape.
This is Dr. Stevens.
- Do you remember me, Charlie?
- Kind of.
- That's good.
Do you remember signing up?
- How'd I do?
- We just let the parole board go.
How do you feel?
- My head hurts.
Amy, can you get him something for his head?
- Wow!
No, no, no, wait a minute. That's her.
- Calm down.
- No. Don't. Fuck you!
Don't tell me to calm down.
- Charlie you don't know what's going on.
- Look, look. That's her.
- It's not her.
- Turn the fuck around! That's her!
- Listen, no, no, no, no.
Our patients will sometimes project people
they see into the simulation.
It's not her.
- That's her.
It's her.
- Just think about it, Charlie.
You saw her when we were prepping you.
- No.
No, that's...
You fucking cunt whore.
You set me up.
- You made the choice.
- No. That's not true. You-
You interfered.
You threw yourself onto me!
- You just couldn't help yourself,
could you?
- That's enough.
- What do you think is going to
happen if you do...
You said you... was she in control?
- No, it's mostly you.
It's all from your head.
We just interjected here.
- No.
You said that this was therapy and that
I would have a chance to commute.
To walk.
- No.
- And then you threw her in here.
- I said you might avoid the chair.
I never said you'd walk.
- You set me up!
You fucking bitch!
You fucking cunt whore!
- You did good.
- Thank you for letting me do it.
- She did good, right?
- I think she did too good.
- How do you like working at the asylum?
- I like it.
- Who do we have next?
- David Zajanski.
- Jesus Christ.
- As we move these patients through
the simulations,
they are forced to confront the
humanity of their actions.
They are broken down and rebuilt
into compassionate, fully functional
human beings,
full of empathy and kindness.
Someone whom you'd be happy
to have as a neighbor,
a schoolteacher, a friend.
- Dr. Stevens.
Hi, Ron Weissman.
I wanted to get you on record
for a story I'm doing.
- At Neuroscape Therapeutics,
we are not only tackling psychopathy
and pioneering criminal justice reform,
but also addressing broader
societal issues.
- So there are some critics that are voicing
concerns about your program.
- Are there?
- Letting these types of people just relive
their most notorious crimes
over and over again, don't you think
that's a little weird
for the families and their victims?
- Our thought recalibration programs
can correct harmful wrong-think patterns
and foster a more empathetic and
enlightened community.
- Look, this isn't real.
It's in their heads, simulations,
same as if they were fantasizing
in their prison cell.
- Yes, but from the victims' perspective...
- Look, Roy?
- Ron.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
we need a medic!
- The best thing we can do to
honor these victims
is to find a way to end this affliction.
- You said you got close.
Have you been able to get any of
their sentences commuted?
- Our results have been very promising.
- This is more than a solution
for psychopathy.
This is a promise for a better future
and a better society.
- One last question.
The critics say that this is nothing but
cruel and unusual punishment.
Are there any side effects?
- Who are these critics, by the way?
All of our patients are volunteers,
and no, we haven't observed
any side effects.
- Excuse me.
Do you have credentials?
- Of course.
I lift them in my car.
- You should get them.
- Thank you for being here today.
And together, let's walk forward
into this new world.
(applause)
- He hasn't slept.
He hasn't slept in days.
- It's okay.
I have nothing for him.
- No, no, no!
I can't sleep!
- The Killer Cafe has a way.
Where just desserts served every day.
Say hi to my mom.
(screams)
♪ (Hard Rock) ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah. ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Oh, my head's hanging lower than my shoulders ♪
♪ Won't ya come help me? ♪
♪ Take a good look at the ground down below that ♪
♪ Devil's gonna meet me. ♪
♪ Wanna take 'em down low ♪
♪ Wanna take 'em down slow ♪
♪ This death's gonna be sweet ♪
♪ Oh, Lord I know where I'm going ♪
♪ This one's on me ♪
♪ Let it be ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah. ♪
♪ This death's gonna be sweet. ♪
♪ Oh, Lord, this death's gonna be sweet. ♪
♪ Oh, dear friend, your life's
gonna be good ♪
♪ and you've been a good man. ♪
♪ And a good book did you take a good look ♪
♪ what it means to have a good plan? ♪
♪ Try and take my money, try
and take my heart, ♪
♪ try and pull the right foot in me. ♪
♪ Oh, yes, sir, your health is a-coming. ♪
♪ This death's gonna be sweet. ♪
♪ Gonna be sweet. Yeah. ♪
♪ Yeah. ♪
♪ Oh, Lord, this death's gonna be sweet. ♪
♪ Oh, your head's hanging lower than your shoulders ♪
♪ Bet ya feeling empty ♪
♪ Look at the ground down below ♪
♪ now your life won't affect me. ♪
♪ Devil, take him down slow. ♪
♪ Devil, take him down low. ♪
♪ This sin is gonna be free. ♪
♪ Oh, Lord, I know where I'm going. ♪
♪ Heaven's gonna greet me. ♪
♪ Now set him free. ♪
♪ Sweet death, set him free. ♪
♪ Yeah. ♪
♪ Oh, sweet, death, set him free. ♪
♪ This death's gonna be sweet. ♪